export const skills = [
  'HTML5',
  'CSS3',
  'Figma',
  'MaterialUI',
  'SASS',
  'Javascript',
  'React',
  'Redux',
  'Single Page Apps',
  'RESTful API',
  'Agile Method',
  'GIT',
  'Github',
  'Jest',
  'Cypress',
  'SQLLite',
  'PostGreSQL',
  'Node',
  'ExpressJS',
  'Python',
  'Algorithms',
  'Async JavaScript',
  'Authentication',
  'Automated Unit Testing',
  'Big-O Notation',
  'Data Structures',
  'Debugging',
  'Deployment',
  'End-To-End Testing'
]
export const questions = [
  {
    question:'Who am I?',
    answer:''
  },{
    question:'What am I currently doing and how did I get here?',
    answer:'I recently graduated from Lambda School, completing both the User Experience Design and Full Stack Web Developement courses, and am now looking for a career in Software Engineering where I can apply my new skills to get people what they need.'
  },{
    question:'Whats my favorite aspect about software?',
    answer:'I love building software that is easy for the user while also standing out from the crowd in terms of design. The ever changing land scape of the industry is prefect for my constant need for stimulation and improvement.'
  },{
  //   question:'What is my biggest personal accomplishment?',
  //   answer:'A long time ago, I got in an accident and lost motor function in half of my body. After a painful amount of work and determination, I have regained most '
  // },{
    question:'What am I looking for right now?',
    answer:'I am new in the industry, but eagar to learn more to build new applications and contribute to the ever evoling tech world. The constant evolution of the industry calls to my perpetual love of learning and my.'
  },{
    question:'Why did I get into Software Development?',
    answer:'Shortly after I started learning UXD, I grew an interest in code, which quickly took over my studies and has had me captivated ever since. '
  },{
  //   question:'What did I do before I got into tech?',
  //   answer:'I worked as a Safeway Night Operations Manager for over 4 years learning various leadership and professional interpersonal skills.'
  // },{
    question:'Where do I see myself in 5 years?',
    answer:'A senior level engineer at your company, working on a project that will improve upon the lives of our customers.'
  },//{
  //   question:'Why is web developement important to me?',
  //   answer:'The internet is where everyone has a voice. It is the great equalizer in this era,  and I want to help spread meassages that are worthy of being heard.'
  // },{
  //   question:'',
  //   answer:' I started my professional journey in retail, working my way up to Night Operations Manager. I qucikly learned and excelled at helping my clients with what ever problems they might have, but it wasnt enough for me. I knew I could do more, and have my work affect more than the person directly in front of me.'
  // },{
  //   question:'',
  //   answer:''
  // },{
  //   question:'',
  //   answer:''
  // },{
  //   question:'',
  //   answer:''
  // },{
]
